Hugh M. Hutton Papers
Hugh M. Hutton Papers
- Work by Others
  - Original cartoon artwork
    - Pierre Bellocq, 11" x 14" (Oversize 39)
Wallace, George B29-B32 B34-B36 B38
Wallace, Henry B1 B38
war B1 B5 B20 B25
War on Poverty B34
Washington, George B2 B5 B8 B13 B16-B18 B21 B23 B25 B28 B30 B34-B36
water supply B7 B9 B26 B31 B33
weapons B2 B7
weather B1 B3 B5 B7 B9-B11 B13-B14 B16-B19 B21-B22 B24-B25 B28 B30-B34 B36-B38
welfare B27
white supremacy B4 B15 B20 B33 B35
White, Harry Dexter B7
Wilhelm II (Germany) B2
Williams, G. Mennen B2
Willkie, Wendell B1
Wilson, Charles B4
Wilson, Harold B32-B33
Wilson, Woodrow B38
Wirtz, W. Willard B29
Wood, Lloyd B10
World War I B1 B4 B7 B10 B15 B23 B34 B38
World War II B1 B11 B13 B15 B22 B27 B30-B31 B37
Yalta Conference B2 B11 B27
Yemen B19
Yugoslavia B34
Zedong, Mao B2 B17 B26-B28 B30-B34 B37-B38
Zhukov, Georgy B13 B18
Zorin, Valerian B3